; ============================= Pages
$SLUTS_pSettings	Settings
$SLUTS_pCustomisation	Customisation
$SLUTS_pDebug	Debug

$SLUTS_difficulty0	Easy
$SLUTS_difficulty1	Normal
$SLUTS_difficulty2	Hard
$SLUTS_difficulty3	Enslaved
; ============================= Settings
$SLUTS_sHaulTypes	Haul Types
$SLUTS_defHaul	Default Cart Haul
$SLUTS_defHaul_info	Weight for the original default Haul to be selected (-> Player dragging buggy cart through Skyrim)
$SLUTS_defHaul	Premium Haul
$SLUTS_defHaul_info	Weight for a premium Haul to be selected (-> Player will deliver special goods to a specific NPC)

$SLUTS_shHauls	Hauls
$SLUTS_sNoTalk	No talking on the job
$SLUTS_sSpontFail	Spontaneous Failure Chance
$SLUTS_sSpontFailRnd	Random Spontaneous Failure Cargo Loss
$SLUTS_sPilfChance	Pilferage Chance
$SLUTS_sPilfChanceIncr	Increase Pilferage Chance for Bandits & Forsworn
$SLUTS_sMaxPilferage	Maximum Pilferarge
	
$SLUTS_shCrime	Crime
$SLUTS_sRehabRate	Rehab Fine Weight
$SLUTS_sRehabRate_Highlight	Difficulty Scale for Rehabilitation System.\nThe higher this is the higher your debt will be relative to how high your bounty was when agreeing to Rehabiliation.
	
$SLUTS_shPayment	Payment
$SLUTS_sBaseCredit	Filly Coins Difficulty Scale
$SLUTS_sOvertimeGrowth	Overtime Difficulty Scale
$SLUTS_sAllDebtToArrears	All debt goes to Arrears
$SLUTS_sMinGoldKept	Minimum gold to keep
	
;	$SLUT_shSimpleSlavery	Simple Slavery
SLUTS_sSSdebtScale	Simple Slavery Difficulty
SLUTS_sSSdebtScale_Highlight	The Difficulty Scale for Simple Slavery. The higher this is, the more you are worth when sold, the more you have to work to regain your freedom!

	
; ============================= Customisation
$SLUTS_chLivery	Livery
;	$SLUTS_cCostumeChoice	Costume Color
;	$SLUTS_cTailChoice	Pony Tail
;	$SLUTS_cYokeChoice	Yoke
$SLUTS_cUseThermal	Use Frostfall Harness
$SLUTS_cThermalColor	Fit Harness Color
$SLUTS_cPonyAnims	Use Ponygirl Animations
$SLUTS_cBoundCombat	Allow Yoke Combat
	
;$SLUTS_chSlaveTats	SlaveTats
$SLUTS_cUseSlutsLivery	Use S.L.U.T.S. Livery?
$SLUTS_cUseUNPLivery	Use UNP textures?
$SLUTS_cUseSlutsColors	Use S.L.U.T.S. Colours?
$SLUTS_cCustomLiveryColor	Use Custom Livery Colour?
$SLUTS_cUseDirt	Use Dirt


; ============================= Debug
$SLUTS_dhHauls	Hauls
$SLUTS_dLargeMsg	Payment/Debt uses MessageBoxes
$SLUTS_dNoRemoveItems	No Player Item Removal
$SLUTS_dDDStruggle	Struggle Anim on Unhitch
	
;	$SLUTS_hDebug	Debug
$SLUTS_dEmergencyTatRemove	Remove Tattoos
$SLUTS_dEmergencyTatRemove_Highlight	This will try to clean off any sticking tattoos.
$SLUTS_dEmergencyTatRemove_Msg	Trying to remove SlaveTats once you exit the MCM.
$SLUTS_removeDD	Remove Quest Devices
$SLUTS_removeDD_Highlight	Remove all S.L.U.T.S. owned DD Quest Items (usually only used during Hauls)
$SLUTS_removeDD_Msg	Unequipping DD Items once you exit the MCM
$SLUTS_dReturnCart	Reset Cart
$SLUTS_dReturnCart_Highlight	Will force the cart back to the player and tether it to them. Useful if you encounter the lovely ''Cart Launches Into Obrit'' bug.\nWILL GLITCH OUT IF USED INSIDE AN INTERIOR LOCATION.
$SLUTS_dReturnCart_Msg	Forcing the Cart back to the player (You can also use Shift+E in game if the cart went flying away). This doesn't work inside an interior zones.\nPlease exit MCM now.
$SLUTS_dSetEssential	Essential When Carting Hack
$SLUTS_dReinitializeMod	Reinitialize
;	$SLUTS_dShowDistance	Show distance between Roots
	
$SLUTS_dhHOTKEYS		HOTKEYS:
$SLUTS_dResetCart	CTRL + E = Detether/Reset Cart
$SLUTS_dTogglePhysics	CTRL + SPACE = Toggle Cart Physics
	
	
	
; ============================= Information
; Settings
$SLUTS_NoTalking_Info	You won't be able to talk to most NPCs while on a delivery. Well you can try, but you'll just get dismissed with a degrading comment.
$SLUTS_SpontFail_Info	Did some ultra stealthy thief poach your cargo without your knowledge? Or maybe you were in such a hurry you didn't notice the cargo being knocked loose on that bumpy road? Set a random chance your perfect run turns out missing cargo anyways.
$SLUTS_SpontFailRandom_Info	If true, \"Spontaneous Failure\" will cause a random amount of cargo loss otherwise it will always cause full Cargo loss.
$SLUTS_TagCart_Info	When enabled your cart will show a quest marker, making it easier to locate if you lose it.
$SLUTS_BaseCredit_Info	The higher this value, the more Filly Coins you earn for each Haul.\nOn Default (2), payment will be between 15.000 & 45.000 Filly Coins. Each additional Point will increase your average payment by ~4.000 Coins
$SLUTS_overtimeGrowth_Info	S.L.U.T.S. loves a commited pony girl willing to put in a little overtime! As long as you're doing it willingly and don't lose any cargo, any additional run after your first will increase the payment you get at the end your haul.\nEach 0.5 Points will increase or decrease this Bonus by roughly 20%
$SLUTS_AllDebtToArrears_Info	If true, debt you accumulate during a Haul will instantly be moved into your Arrears rather than checked against the Gold in your Escrow first.\nThis means that the money you had before a Haul will stay with you and wont be taken away to pay off your debt.
$SLUTS_MinGoldKept_Info	S.L.U.T.S. is a serious and trustworthy business that can't have their employees starving on the street! In case you cant cover the Damage you caused during a Haul out of your own Pocket, S.L.U.T.S. will leave you with this much Gold, so you can at least pay for a warm meal and a bed!\nSet 0 to disable.
$SLUTS_PilfChance_Info	Chance that someone pilfers you when you are assaulted or leave your Goods behind.\nMay be useful to reduce this rate if you've set the game up to where a poor girl can't travel 10 feet without some rape happy psycho having their way with her ( you sicko :p ).
$SLUTS_PilfChanceIncrease_Info	Chance that you will be pilfered is increased if Bandits or Forsworn are assaulting you.
$SLUTS_MaxPilferage_Info	When pilfered, the maximum amount of Goods taken away (from 1.500).\nThis is just an upper cap. The amount taken away will be somewhere between 1 and this value.
$SLUTS_SSminDebt_Info	Minimum amount of debt you can be stuck with after being sold to S.L.U.T.S. by a Simple Slavery Auction. A setting of 0 will still require you to complete 1 run to earn your freedom.\nThe amount of debt you have to work off will be between this setting and \"Maximum Debt\"
$SLUTS_SSmaxDebt_Info	Maximum amount of debt you can be stuck with after being sold to S.L.U.T.S. by a Simple Slavery Auction.\nThe amount of debt you have to work off will be between this setting and \"Minimum Debt\"

; Customisation
;	$SLUTS_CostumeChoice_Info	Customize your base color theme.
;	$SLUTS_TailChoice_Info	Customize your ponytail. No not that type of ponytail...
;	$SLUTS_YokeChoice_Info	Customize your yoke style.\nIF YOU ARE EXPERENCING CRASHES AFTER THE CART SPELL IS CAST ON YOU TRY THE BREAST OR CHAINLESS DESIGN
$SLUTS_UseThermal_Info	When agreeing to perform a haul you will be equipped with a body harness that offers maximum Frostfall body protection.\n!Note that this Setting wont have any effect until you accept your next Haul.
$SLUTS_ThermalFitColor_Info	Should the Thermal Harness use the Color of your Uniform or stay Black?\nFor thoes who prefer the old Color Theme.
$SLUTS_PonyAnims_Info	Toggle whether you will use the Ponygirl movement animations during hauls.\n!Note that this Setting wont have any effect until you accept your next Haul.
$SLUTS_BoundCombat_Info	Toggle whether you are able to use melee combat while restrainted in a S.L.U.T.S. Yoke/Armbinder/cuffs/etc.\n!Note that this Setting wont have any effect until you accept your next Haul.
$SLUTS_UseSlutsLivery_Info	If true, your pony will be magically tattooed with the S.L.U.T.S. livery.
$SLUTS_UseUNPLivery_Info	Use the UNP livery textures. NOTE: Custom colors are now supported for UNP! Just turn off *Use S.L.U.T.S. Colours* and you're good to go :)
$SLUTS_UseSlutsColors_Info	Uses the default bright green color for your livery
$SLUTS_CustomLiveryColor_Info	Choose the color you want for your livery
$SLUTS_UseDirt_Info	Disable/Enable dirt tats after SL Scenes.

; Debug
$SLUTS_LargeMsg_Info	Makes notifications about payments/debt use a large mesage box, requiring confirmation to continue.
$SLUTS_NoRemoveItems_Info	Disables the removal of all the Players items when they agree to start doing a set of runs. Cheating? Probably, but some players were experiencing issues with the item removal feature so here this option is. You will still have all your gold moved to the escrow. You're using it because you're one of those players, not some cheating douchebag, right?
$SLUTS_DDStruggle_Info	Disable Struggle animation when Unhitching from the Cart.
$SLUTS_SetEssential_Info	For some unlucky players the cart will often get tethered to wrong point of the body upon reloading after a death. This will cause the cart to behave in a totally batshit manner until you exit to main menu and reload. This option is a hacked in work around that sets the player to essential while on a haul, which prevents the bug from happening. WARNING: NEVER SAVE AFTER RUNNING OUT OF HEALTH. THIS HACK MAY ALLOW CHEATING. USE THIS HACK AT YOUR OWN RISK!
;	$SLUTS_ShowDistance_Info	Get a notification telling you the Distance between your Dispatch & Destination Root. This is number is meaningless for regular play
$SLUTS_ResetCart_Info	Use to Tether/Untether from your Cart. Can also be used for debugging if the Cart gets stuck.\nWILL GLITCH OUT IF USED INSIDE AN INTERIOR LOCATION.
$SLUTS_TogglePhysics_Info	Disables physic Simulation of the cart. Press again to re-enable.
$SLUTS_SpawnCart_Info	Attempts to delete your old Cart and replaces it with a newly spawned one.\nWILL GLITCH OUT IF USED INSIDE AN INTERIOR LOCATION.